How much is enough, Barquero?
Barquero is a western film directed by Gordon Douglas.
Jake Remy leads a gang of outlaw cutthroats making their
escape toward Mexico from a successful robbery.
Barring their way is a river--crossable only by means of a ferry barge.
The barge operator, Travis, refuses to be bullied into providing transport for the gang and escapes across river
with most of the local populace--leaving Remy and his gang behind, desperately seeking a way across.
A river-wide stand-off begins between the gang and the townspeople, both
groups of which have left people on the wrong side of the river.
Travis, played by Lee Van Cleef.
Jake Remy, played by Warren Oates.
Mountain Phil, played by Forrest Tucker.
Marquette, played by Kerwin Mathews.
Anna, played by Mariette Hartley.
Nola, played by Marie Gomez.
Barquero is a 1970 American Western film starring Lee Van Cleef and Warren
Oates, produced by Hal Klein and directed by Gordon Douglas.
Barquero was Lee Van Cleef's first American-made film
since 1962's How the West Was Won.
It was also his first starring role in an American Western.